All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful
[music] Wednesday, Tuesday afternoon.
God bless everyone in the name of Jesus,
Yeshua, the Messiah. I pray everybody is
super blessed [music] as Bitcoin is now
dumping, guys.
Bitcoin is now dumping down into the
dumps. And the question is,
um, you know, what's going to happen
here? Well, I told you guys what I think
is going to happen yesterday. I told you
guys what I think is going to happen on
Monday. Monday was yesterday. And here's
the thing. I don't even know what day it
is anymore. I really don't know what day
it is, guys, anymore. All right. But we
got to give a major shout out to
everybody in the chat right now. Big
shout out to Get GM9Q.
Big major shout out to Adam Thomas. He
says, "Good morning, Jason." Good
afternoon to you, Adam. You must be over
there on the West Coast. All right, I'm
over here in New York City over here at
the diner with my lady friend Dolores.
[music]
She's bringing out the coffee over here.
She's bringing out the bagels and the
pancakes and the coffee and the cream
cheese and all that. The Bitcoin price
right now is testing the point of
control of the range here. We could see
clearly the point of control of the
range is right here. We're getting a
little bit of a rejection. We're
changing market structure. A little bit
bearish here. We're going to be talking
about it. All right. Short trade. Locked
in five grand on it. Okay. This the
short trade that I've been in since the
uh ominous day where I actually only
closed my long at the exact [music]
high.
But yeah, man. Yeah. Big shout out to
you, Adam Thomas. Big shout out to Bon
Voyage. I lost trading. I lost at
trading 62,000.
You lost at the Bitcoin price of 60,000
or you actually lost $62,000.
Sheesh. 62K. That's a lot of money. I've
lost more. But yeah, that sucks, man.
I'm not going [music] to lie. This is
just a pre- crash pump, says 2025
resurrection. Shout out to Delinquid
YouTube who says, "Yo,
shout out to 2025." He says, "Guys,
please pray that I win the giveaway
today. I really need it." Are we doing a
giveaway today?
>> I guess we're doing a giveaway today.
Yeah, we could do a giveaway today,
guys. You know, Bitbase
is giving away $500 every week. You know
what? I think we're going to do that
giveaway today. Today is the day that we
give away 500 US Donald Trump's.
Big shout out to Caleb Ford who says,
"Yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo."
And shout out to Felix H. Shout out to
John Floss who says, "Good morning."
Good morning to you. Shout out to Crypto
Coons holding it down with the wrench.
Shout out to Glass Hopper7 and Tunosir.
You tell us, are you stupid for shorting
Bitcoin? Yes. Yes, I did tell you that.
I told you, am I stupid for shorting
Bitcoin? Guys, there's a poll in the
chat. The question is, am I stupid for
shorting Bitcoin? And the possible
answers to the question are either,
let's see here. Hang on. I'm having I'm
having a really hard time operating this
system here. The the
you know I have to move myself out of
the way here. The the the possible
answers are am I stupid for shorting 80K
60K car from the moon or yes. 13% of you
think I'm stupid. And you know what? If
I saw this screenshot right here, in
fact, let's just take it.
Okay, I would also agree with you.
Honestly, if I saw this,
um I would think to myself, you know
what? This man is absolutely [__]
[music]
All right. There's something wrong with
the brain. He must be stupid. You know,
I don't know what else to say about it.
Um, so 13% I have to say I I kind of
agree with you guys. The 50% the 51%
that say 60K, I also say, you know what,
I kind of agree with you guys too. I
could see Bitcoin getting moved down to
60K right around here [music] where my
this this TP is here. Okay, I also could
agree with you there.
>> [music]
>> And we'll we'll discuss we will discuss
guys because again this this is getting
pretty dang juicy
uh with with the this uh this lower low
that we're making here. You know, the
Bitcoin price is officially breaking
down from Z Chanel. All right. And kind
of getting a back test. I mean,
depending on how you want to pull this
little trend line here, maybe we're even
getting a little bit of a back test. Oh,
man. And we could go for that liquidity
way down below. Um,
I washed my bathroom today and cousin
Kevin gave me candies. That's nice that
you washed your bathroom. You know, I
washed
my bathroom today and uh, my cousin
Kevin didn't give me candies. He gave me
undies. He gave me a fresh pair of
undies. Chafing. No chafing with the
undies I wear now, guys. All right. Um,
shout out to Kevin Walsh, guys, because
here's the thing. In the midst of all
this, also tomorrow we do have Kevin
Walsh, the man himself coming out of the
closet in place of our old friend Jerome
Powell to tell us about the interest and
the inflation and all this kind of
stuff. And um yeah, so it's going to get
it's going to get volatile tomorrow.
Man, are we being set up for a long
squeeze to the $60,000? Very possible.
Um
Dr. Coach says, "All right, Jay, release
the API keys for bots on Antarctic or
else I'll chop off my Fibonacci
extension."
My goodness, sounds painful. Look, it's
all in good time. All in due time, my
friend. All in due time. All right. All
in due time. Let's see who else we got
in the chat today. Enjoy being says,
"Show me the chickens." Well, here's the
thing, guys. It is rainy out today. It
is so stormy out today. I don't know if
you guys Can you guys even see this?
Let's see if we can see this.
Look at how gray and and dismal it looks
out there today, guys. Honestly, do do
you see that? How gray and dismal it is
today. So, I am not going to show you
the chickens. But I do have some good
news, guys. Cong. Praise the Lord and
congratulations to the new mother
because we do have new baby chicks on on
the Casper on the Casper farmstead. We
have new baby chicks. So cute. So cute.
Let me show you. Let me show you a
picture. Oh, let me show you a picture.
Oh, man. I'm a proud I'm I'm a proud
chicken papa. They call me Jay the
chicken papa. First of all, I'll show
you this picture of one of the eggs
hatching. And then I'll show you a
picture of a, you
man. Oh man, I love baby chicks. Baby
chicks. Who doesn't love baby chicks?
Put a two in the chat if you hate baby
chicks.
Do you guys hate baby chicks or do you
love baby chicks? I love baby chicks.
They're so cute. There there's nothing
like a baby chick. Oh man, I just
totally doxed all myself. [music]
I guess I can't show you the baby chicks
without doxing myself. So hang on one
second here.
Um,
yeah. All right. Well, you know what? I
guess I can't show you a picture of Baby
Chick without doxing myself, so
whatever. I already doxed it anyway. You
guys now all know all my dirty secrets.
Let's see. Uh, I enjoy being says, "Show
me the chickens. I can't show you." All
right, doxed myself. Shout out to Bor PC
guy. When did I enter short? I entered
short on um on the 21st of July. All
right. I entered short as a hedge
against my [music] long trade. Okay. I
have been in the short trade since uh
the [music] the um the 21st July at 1211
and 38 seconds. All right. So, just to
quickly go over the history here of of
of Jason Casper's trading. Okay. Jason
Casper. All right. We [music] were we
were in basically we're in this long
trade. Okay, we're in a swing long
trade. Two short scalps that were hedges
got stopped out for a small loss. I
accidentally closed the long trade at
the exact top on the 20 uh the 21st of
July. The 21st of July. at the exact
top. I accidentally closed this trade
live and I was so frustrated that I
closed the trade that I that I flop and
groped trying to now get back long and I
I gave back $11,000 of my hard-earned
profit.
All right, so that's what happened here.
I should have You know what?
Yeah, I I had some bad trade. I even
made I made a video about it on Friday
or Sunday, I forget, where I talked
about my trading psychology and how I
lost $11,000 because of my own
stupidity, my own emotions, my own
greed, my own revenge trading, not
sticking to the plan, not listening to
Senor when he told me not to do it, and
I did it anyway. not taking profit when
I should have taken profit because I was
taking scalp longs and I was trying to
hold them because I thought we were
going to 74k
but because I shorted the exact top as
well
now thankfully I've made back 5,000 of
my $11,000 loss here and so all in all
you know what what do you say 11 11
yeah that's like 15 grand so you know 60
that's like45 $5,000 in profit even
though I made so many stupid mistakes.
So, I'll take it, man. But sheesh.
Um, the egg code has got you there.
Actually, you know, I I don't think I
can actually do an egg code today
without showing everything on my
computer screen. All right.
Um,
most people think I'm wrong. I'm most
likely right. Well, here's the thing. I
don't know if I'm right or wrong, guys.
You know, that's another thing. I never
know if I'm right or wrong. [music] All
right? I'm just taking the dang trades.
What's with the 15minute time switch
lately? I'm doing a little experiment
with the YouTube algorithm. I don't know
if I should talk about it. Uh, this is
pre-recorded. Yes, Synth One, you're
right. This is pre-recorded. [music]
Now, now to my defense. Is this not the
best pre-recorded live you've ever seen
in your life where I have the mental
foresight to answer your comment?
Thank you, Synth One, for collaborating
with me to make it seem like this is
live, but don't tell anybody else this
is pre-recorded.
An an AI pre-record. All right, big
shout out to Backup Hero in the chat.
Shout out to Senor
and [music] um let's see who else.
Senor, man, God bless you, bro. Am I
going live for FOMC tomorrow? Of course.
Isn't my name Jason Casper?
Shout out to Wendell from Hawaii.
And shout out to Bullish on Parade.
He says, "It's merely a retest,
gentlemen. Hold the line." Are you
talking about a bullish retest? Back
test the PC. You know, yeah, we're we're
going to do a $500 giveaway today, guys.
You know,
Rose Kite says, "I'm looking fine
today." You know why I'm looking fine
today? First of all, I got the sideways
purple douchebag hat. Second of all,
it's because I finally figured out I
finally figured out I finally figured
out how to get this stupid AI camera
from tracking my face everywhere I go.
So now I don't have to worry about
what's going on over here, what's going
on over here. I don't need to worry
about everyone seeing all my all my
stuff, you know, cuz cuz this camera
stays fixed like a fixed range volume
profile. [music]
All right. Um,
anything we can do to get Jerome P back?
Sadly no. [music] Sadly no. All right.
Sadly no. Um
you can see the position out there in
the trees. [music]
Weather looks bearish. Yeah, it does.
Chart looks more bullish than bearish.
Crypto rig. All right. Well, we'll see.
Okay. [music] We'll have to see. No, not
a newborn baby Casper. Not yet. There is
a newborn baby Casper on the way. All
right. All right. There's a newborn baby
Casper on the way. Praise the Lord.
[music] But that the newborn baby Cass
won't be here for a few months. All
right. For a few months.
Uh,
you know, uh,
we have haters in the house. [music] I
don't see haters. Maybe they got blocked
by the the mods. God bless the mods.
[music] All right. God bless the mods.
You like chicken nuggets? Dream Tanks TV
loves chicken nuggets. Um.
Um. [music]
20.
Yeah, 26x trades. That's the way to go.
That's the way to go. All right. Yeah,
Senor tried to tell me that
that I shouldn't be longing. And he was
right, man. Senor, you were right, bro.
But look, there comes a time in every
man's life where he has to he has to pay
the price for his own emotions. You know
what I'm saying? Um,
shout out to Samu
in the house.
Is this live run on my treadmill? No,
it's walked on my treadmill. Shout out
to the real Don D.
He says, "Name the baby Vitalic." No, I
already have the names [music] for my
baby. If it's a male or a female baby, I
don't [music] know. I don't know.
Another day, another Casper baby. It
really seems that way. Michelle Aliser,
you know, there's something. I have a
problem here. I definitely have a
problem with making a lot of babies. I
can't help myself. I just can't help it.
It just happens. [music]
It just happens. Even I could try not to
make a baby and I and I make a baby. I I
don't know. I don't know. I don't know
how that happens. All right.
Shout out to Dave Digital in the house.
Shout out to Nalis UK drum and bass. Um,
dump Bitcoin, says Real Cipher Rider.
Let's go. Dump the Bitcoin, baby. Let's
go. A retest of the trend line. Oh,
yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, guys. Not only a
retest of the trend line, but a retest
of the dang point of control. I mean,
yeah. Let's discuss. Let's shall we pop
into Shall we pop into the charts, guys?
Quick reminder, we're giving a $500
giveaway today on Bitbase.
Bitbase is giving away $500 today, guys.
And not only that, but uh Blofen
Blofin is giving away $2,000
a week. All right. So, last week, these
four people won $500 each on Blofin.
Every week, Blofin's giving away $2,000.
$2,000 to four winners split. So that's
$500 a week for four people plus our
Bitbase $500 giveaway. So overall, we're
giving away $2,500 a week on this
channel and all you have to do is sign
up to Bitbase. Sign up to Blowin.
If you want to win the Blowofin
giveaway, you have to join my Discord
and follow the rules for the Blofin
giveaway. It's a you could join the free
or the paid Discord. Does not matter.
Does not matter. The Mad Hatter, he's
eating chicken from a platter.
chicken from a platter.
Yeah, we do have a population crisis.
It's because Jason Casper can't stop
making babies. I mean, sheesh, man. I
just can't stop. No matter how hard I
try, I don't know what the deal is. I
don't know what the deal is, guys. I'm
I'm I'm baffled. I'm ba I'm I'm not even
kidding. I'm baffled. It's as crazy as
what like when I closed the trade, I
just couldn't believe what happened. I
couldn't believe I closed the trade.
It's the same with making all these
babies. I can't believe I'm making all
these babies. How's this possible? How's
this possible? I have a whole town that
lives in my house, guys. I mean,
seriously, I'm not even kidding. It's
It's insane. It's insane. Um, but here's
the deal. Okay, here is the deal. We're
We're popping on over to the Bitcoin
chart here, and yesterday we had marked
out two very important areas of support
and resistance. All right, the major
area of support is down here at the
$60,000 level. We'll call it the $60,000
level.
All right, this is the value area low of
the range. Golden pocket 786.
And then our major resistance, of
course, was back at the high of this
range. Now, we were keeping our eye on
this very important line yesterday. And
I said yesterday, so long as we're
holding above this white line, then I
expect higher prices. But especially if
we close a daily candle and we make a
lower low, right? Cuz we're in an
uptrend. We have our lower, higher,
higher, lower, higher, higher, higher,
lower, higher, higher, higher, lower,
higher, higher, higher, low, lower high.
I said, look, as long as we're holding
this, that's all good cuz we haven't
made a lower low yet. But guess what?
Last night, lower low. My goodness. And
so now we're below the PC of the range.
Now, why is this a big deal? This is a
big deal because this is everything
we've traded, guys, since February,
the end of January, the beginning of
February.
The majority of the volume is now above
us. All right. Now, that being said, I I
do think that that makes it probable now
that we continue to take this liquidity.
We continue to stop hunt these lows.
We've officially broken the trend line.
We've officially switched into bearish
market structure here. And there are a
lot of stop- losses below this low right
here, which we didn't take. This low
right here, which we didn't take. This
these lows right here, which we didn't
take. And so if we take that, we come
right into our key support back test the
major support resistance flip in this
box and then we can look for a long back
to the top of the range. That is what I
feel like is is most likely to happen.
Now, now that being said, I'm going to
be very transparent. The short trade
that I took from here on the 21st of
July, I have taken profit.
I have secured a profit for the first
time this whole time since July 21st. I
did not take a profit. I did not take a
profit here. Did not take a profit here.
Did not take a profit here. What I've
done now is I've added to my position
and I've closed half the trade. Okay.
Why did I do this? Because I don't know
for certain if we're going to come all
the way down here and I I'm doing this
to make money. So, I have put myself now
in a position where I'm guaranteed to
make a few thousand no matter what.
Okay? So, I'm not here to say we're 100%
coming down there. I'm saying it's
probable. I'm expecting it. I'm holding
a short trade right now, $200,000.
Looking for my next target down here at
around $60,000. But nothing's
guaranteed, right? Nothing is
guaranteed. So really, it comes down to
this PC. All right? And the problem with
PC's is they are fair [music] price.
This is as fair price as fair price can
be since February, right?
This is fair price. Well, what does that
mean? When we come to fair price, a lot
of times we chop around fair price and
we could spend weeks saying, "Oh, we're
bullish. We're bearish. We're bullish.
We're bearish. We're bullish. We're
bearish. We're bullish. We're bearish."
And that very well may happen here.
Okay? That very well may happen here cuz
let's say we close the daily candle back
above the PC and back inside the trend
line. Well, then it's just highest
probability here, right? So to avoid
getting chopped up, what we need to do
is pretty much we just need to be
patient, right? We should be looking for
long trades at the lows and short trades
at the highs. And if we are looking for
a short trade right now, I mean, I would
say that technically speaking, there is
a valid entry because we've done this,
right? Because we've done this because
we've lost and back test that PC.
Technically speaking, there is a valid
entry here with almost a 3:1 risk-reward
ratio, but it's not the most highest
probability setup, right? A valid trade
doesn't mean it's high probability. The
idea of this trade is we've lost the
trend line. We've lost the PC. We're
back testing it. We give it a little
playroom to get the full back test. And
then we're targeting value area low of
the range. Right? Just like technically
speaking earlier this week, we had a
valid long trade when we [music] bounced
from the PC, made a higher low, and then
we had something like this where we
could have targeted up to the top.
Right? Now, of course, this trade ended
up getting stopped out, right? Because
trading from the PC, [music] it's fair
price, right? We you can't always expect
the best moves like you can if you're
trying to long the low of the range or
short the high of the range, right? But
nonetheless, this is valid. And this is
kind of what I'm hoping and and and
preparing to happen next. Now, if we
come down to $60,000, then what? Well,
the weekly time frame, like we've been
saying, has confirmed the bullish
divergence,
right? The twoe time frame is printing a
bullish divergence, which will confirm
at the end of the week depending on what
happens. Our 4day has bullish divergence
at the low. Money flow is continuing to
come up here. What does that mean about
the money flow? Well, when you have a
bottom like this, all right, a bottom
like what? a bottom like this. All
right, [music] where the price is coming
down to a key zone of support. In this
case, the key zone of support is the
macro Fibonacci gold in the pocket from
the bare market bottom to the bull
market top at $57.8,000.
And we're seeing market cipher B as the
price is getting lower. Market cipher B
is getting higher. Right, we have our
left butt cheek. We have our right butt
cheek, right? Just like Dolores at the
diner coming out. Left butt cheek big,
right butt cheek skinny. Price comes
down, price gets a bounce. Now once that
price gets a bounce well [music] what
typically happens is that means the
bottom signal is in okay and that next
trigger wave that we get the next
trigger wave that we get like this is
going to give us a powerful move to the
upside. This is a this whole entire
structure here would be a bullish
structure on market cipher B. bullish
divergence at the key support, money
flow cross,
momentum coming back up, and then this
next trigger wave that we print down
here with continued direction [music] as
we make a higher low. That is a bullish
signal that could take us back to the
top of the range. That's exactly
actually what I would suspect, which is
why if we do come down here, I'm
actually looking to compound this long
trade, add to the long trade, put this
20 grand back into the position. Of
course, this is leverage here. So, we're
probably going to be putting like $250
onto the trade. We'll be in a half
million position
and hopefully take that thing back up
towards, you know, the $67,000 level or
beyond. All right? Because if we flip
67K, we could get a move up to 74. All
right? We flip 74, we get a move up to
82. Right? It's that simple. I'm not
saying it's going to happen, but the
reality is, you know, if we flip levels,
then that's the probability. Just like
now we've lost the PC. So the
probability is well we're coming down to
60K. All right.
Coming down yonder to good old 60K. Will
the Bulls and the Bears come out to
play?
Coming on down to 60K.
Will the Bulls and the Bears come out to
play? You know,
coming on [music] down. Coming on down.
Coming on down.
If you're feeling tired, chug 500 g of
coffee.
Sounds pretty crazy
and I wouldn't do that, my friend. Um,
I wouldn't [music] do that.
You know, these trend lines always break
and nothing happens. Just sideways for
years. Inward curvature.
We do have inward curvature on the
yellow VWOP. But here's the thing. Even
with the inward curvature on the yellow
VWOP, are you talking about the 4-day
day digital or are you talking about the
weekly? Talking about the weekly. What
time frame are you talking about? Now,
someone did ask, "What about the bullish
div on the 4hour time frame? Is this
what you're talking about? The inward
curvature here?" This 4hour time frame
inward curvature looking like she wants
to do the old flaperoni.
This is a nice divergence on the 4 hour.
[music] Uh, I'm not going to lie, it is
a nice div on the 4 hour. Um,
it's a little ambiguous here because we
had massive money flow divergence at
this high. Now, we have momentum
divergence here. If we can't reclaim the
PC,
I wouldn't be surprised if this does
curve back down and we come down even
lower here. Um,
but yeah, I it is possible for this
4hour bullish divergence to pump us all
the way back up to the top of the range.
And if that happens, rest assured, I am
going to be looking for a short trade up
here. Like, I really am. I'm going to be
looking for a short
if I take one, you know, and I I'll let
the Casper crew know like I do. All
right. I'll let the Casper crew know
like I do. But but yeah, that is that is
the one bullish thing right here about
this chart is the 4hour bullish diver
right here. All right. Trade disclaimer
needs an I. Did I miss a letter? I'm
sorry.
Is anyone feeling tired today? Cuz I'll
tell you, I feel pretty dang good today,
guys. Yesterday I was tired. All right.
So, I've been going way too hard in the
gym. I've been going too hard in the
gym. I've been chasing
the dopamine. I I don't know what else
to say. I get addicted to to exercise
because it makes me [music] feel good or
it makes me feel good. There's something
about starting your day with the with
the cortisol. There's something about
starting your day with an insane rush of
adrenaline and dopamine and pushing
heavy weight. And the problem is, you
know, it's like everything else in life.
You know, eventually it's the law of
diminishing returns and you're chasing
that high and you can't get high anymore
and you just wear yourself down to the
ground. And yesterday, that's how I
felt. So, I slept a lot yesterday. I ate
a lot yesterday. I took a nap this
morning, ate a lot today. I'm already
450 carbohydrates deep, baby. Probably
going to hit over 800 carbs today, you
know.
But, uh, yeah. Have I looked at Etherum
on the 6 hour? No. We will take a look
at Etherum. There's no div on the 4
hour. Are you kidding me? I mean, do you
do you not see what my eyes see? How
much do I bench? Pitifully pitiful
amounts of bench. I haven't done the
flat bench press in in a long time. But
if I were to guess my flat bench press
max right now probably would be like
280.
I could I could probably bench 275 maybe
for a double.
My max ever is only 330. And that was
when I was really trying to bench press
a lot. But yeah, I've always been really
weak at at presses, right? I've been
very weak at presses.
I've been nursing a torn meniscus. Dang,
Senor,
I'm so sorry to hear that, man. May the
Lord bless you with a speedy recovery.
How come my PC is at 64 cryptoz? is
because I'm using the bybit inverse
perpetual USD chart and this is the only
chart that should be used for trading
Bitcoin in my opinion. All right, but
other people have different charts and
that's fine. All right,
275 pounds, not kilograms. I don't even
know what a kilogram is. All right, I'm
an American. I'm an American. Let's take
a look at Ethereum.
Um, [music] we also have a change of
market structure on the 1 hour. We're
trying to hold the VWAP from the low.
Actually, I think I'm pretty sure. Yeah,
you're right. So, that's that's one last
thing that we we should talk about here.
So far, this anchor VWOP from the low
has been our support throughout the
entirety of this channel. And right now,
as our friend says, we're trying to hold
it. We lost it. And locally here, I'm
not going to lie, we we have a really
nice like low here, CDW, right? We
formed a mini range. We come down to the
12-minut time frame. This mini range
actually, wow, gave us a really bullish
looking divergence here. I haven't I
haven't looked at these low time frame.
This looks really nice here. This CDW,
this chicken's drinking water pattern,
right? And so, yeah, holding above this
anchored VWAP actually is is pretty
nice. Uh, but losing it is bad because
this has been our support, guys, for the
entirety of this channel here. So, are
we doing something similar to what we've
done in the past where we lose it and
reclaim it and pump? It's very possible.
And I do have to say I have to tweak my
bias a little bit because the 12-minut
time frame is my bread and butter here.
[music] And same same with the 24minut.
We have some very bullish looking
bottoms here on these lower time frames.
So with that being said,
let's actually do a little low time
frame analysis here. Let's do a little
bit of low time frame analysis. I you
know what I would even entertain right
now with scalp long coming down to back
test 63k
and either either do this [music] or you
know do this. I would I would entertain
an an entry from that level. In fact,
I'm going to go ahead and set me a
little alert.
I'm going to set me a little bit of an
alert here.
You know, I I can't set an alert here.
What What the actual, man? What What is
going on here? Hang on. I have to save
the dang thing that [laughter] this is
so insane. What is going on? Oh man.
There we go. Let me let me set myself a
little bit of an alert here. 63K, you
know, that's the way. 63K. Hey, hey,
hey, hey. Have I started accumulating on
spot? Absolutely I have. Absolutely.
You know, um,
of course, why not Bitcoin USDT? I just
like the I just like inverse perpetual.
You know what I'm saying?
How much do I weigh? Well, as of this
morning, I weigh 199.9bs,
which
sadly, guys, the sad this it's the sad
thing is I I was up to 215
in March. All right, I bulked up to 215.
I put on some weight. All right, [music]
I cut down to like
199. Cut down to 199. I lost about 15
pounds.
All right. And then I tried to eat I
tried to
I tried to eat a little bit more and I
was and I got myself back up to like 205
consistently for a few weeks which is
where I kind of wanted to be. I wanted
to be around 205, right? 205 pretty dang
lean. All right. 205 abs popping. All
right. [music]
But because I've been going too hard in
the gym, I'm back down to 199.
All right. So I've been going too hard,
you know. So that's kind of a bummer.
The reason why it's a bummer is because
I'll tell you. All right, not that like
anyone cares except for me. In 2025
in February, I was about as lean as I am
now at about 195 lbs. So, I thought I
gained 10 lbs of muscle. That's what I
thought actually happened. It was
probably just water. It's probably just
water. I probably gained like four
pounds of muscle cuz I tried really hard
these last [music] few years to put on
some strength, put on some muscle, push
the calories,
but [music] uh looks like I didn't do
the best job here. You know what's the
maximum losing streak I've ever had? I
don't know. I have some crazy losing
streaks. You guys have seen my chat
gpted P&L. I have like a 40 38% win
rate. [music] Um
you know what I'm saying? Um,
I'm not getting abs. One month's trying.
[music]
Well, here's the thing. I'm a fat
person. I'm morbidly obese. I'm morbidly
obese. [music] And uh, so here's the
thing. I started trying to get abs when
I was a teenager. All right? I started
trying to get abs when I was like 16
years old or so. 15, 16. All right? And
I didn't have abs until I was like
29.
I didn't have abs until I was 29,
you know.
So, it takes more than a month, man.
Especially if you're fat like me. If
you're fat and weak,
you know, just like Jason Casper. Jason
Casper, I have the fattest, weakest
[music]
genetics you could possibly ask for.
It's crazy. It's so crazy,
you know. But look, it just goes to show
if you're consistent and you eat healthy
and you lift and you take it seriously,
[music] even a fat, obese weakling like
me,
>> you can get abs. You know what I'm
saying?
You can't be a man if you're not 200 lb.
I know. Well, I'm 199.9. I'm this close.
I'm this close to being an alpha, but
I'm still a beta. Hence the purple
sideways hat.
All right, let's take a look at
Ethereum.
Man, things are getting so serious with
this beat, though, guys. You know, this
beat really gets me fired up every time.
It gets me fired up every single time.
We have to take a look at ETH, though.
But [clears throat] we're above the PC.
Yeah, we're above the PC. Man, this beat
gets me fired up.
Uh uh uh uh uh.
Man.
Hey yo. Hey [music] yo. J Casper. I'm so
dang fired up taking trades like you
know I've had enough. [music]
199.9 your boy ain't tough. Still a beta
male but you know we're coming back
rough. [music]
Say casher. We're in the house shorting
Bitcoin. What a clown looking like a
mouse. We're [music] coming out and
we're sitting on the couch looking like
we won. So dang lazy like a cloud. They
said yo hit the gym baby. Time to get it
in baby. But we pump up maybe baby maybe
we begin to shoot up [music] like a nice
rocket. Bitcoin straight to the golden
pocket. Yeah, I got [music] the purple
hat sideways, bars in my head, taking
trades all the days cuz we do it the
same way every single other day. I give
it to you straight and know I never give
a day. Fake cash is [music] so serious
he never play. Cinnamon buns, you know
that's the way. Take the sugar and the
drizzle and you put it on top. Bitcoin
price drop the pump, it hits the spot
[music] and then we rock it to be top.
Can you spot it? Market makers coming in
just like Sonic versus Robotic. Throw
the rocket, then we drop it [music] cuz
you know we never stop it. Uh Jay
Casher, he's so hot. And we got the
beats, we got the bars, we got the cars.
We're going far straight to Mars like
Space X [music] dumping down to the
ground. The Bitcoin price. Can you hear
the sound?
[music]
>> Yeah, this beat gets me fired up, baby.
It gets me fired up. Let's take a look
at Etherum. All right.
Um,
so here's the deal. Someone said, "Take
a look at ETH on the 6th hour."
So, I got to change the speed, otherwise
I won't be able to focus.
Here we go. Much much calmer.
So, we do have a we have a pretty uh
bearish looking divergence here
on the 6 hour.
We have this guy, right? We've taken the
liquidity here. We actually have a
double drive of divergence, right?
Because this technically here was
divergence. Now we got this divergence.
Um let's go down to the 4 hour.
The 4 hour has no divergence. 4 hour has
a bearish divergence.
[music] So here's the deal with ETH
right now, guys. This PC is going to be
a key level. So long as we hold, let's
call it,
I mean, we can't. ETH does not like
exact levels. All right. ETH has no
respect of exact levels here.
As long as we hold $1,800,
that is technically bullish. And if not,
then I would be looking at this whole
thing as our sideways range here. All
right. So, let's let's clear off all
this and let's just look at this as our
sideways range. This is going to be our
range high. All right. If we Bart
Simpson pattern this, this is our range
low down here. And so really, here's
what we got. All right, here's what we
got. From range low to range high, our
Fibonacci golden pocket is coming in
around this back test area. This would
be the support that we would get that we
would come to if we're going to lose
$1,800. We would come down to around
this area, honestly. All right. Um, you
could see how easily we could long
squeeze that, take the liquidity
Right? Very similar to what's happening
with Bitcoin with the Bitcoin channel.
Right? We're already breaking down from
the Bitcoin channel. This is the
Ethereum channel. We would probably come
down to this area where we could look
for a bounce. If we pull our fixed range
volume profile,
ah, you know, the sad thing is we would
probably actually end up coming down a
little bit lower to this zone here
toward value area low, honestly. Uh, if
we're going to lose 1,800.
Uh, and of course, the other place to
look would be coming back down to the
$1,500 level at the exact bottom of the
range. Now, this the thing about ETH
that's different from Bitcoin is ETH
does not have the nice bullish
divergence bottom here. So, on Bitcoin
at the bottom of the Bitcoin range, we
have a clear bullish bottom signal. We
don't have that for ETH, but ETH does
not give us clear signals as Bitcoin
does, but they do kind of follow each
other, right? So, if Bitcoin is going to
continue down to $60,000, it just makes
the most sense that ETH would come back
down toward $1,600, right? If Bitcoin is
going to break the range to the downside
and take the liquidity, well, it makes
the most sense that ETH would probably
do the same. Let's check out our daily
time frame. The daily time frame looks
bullish on market cipher B. Even though
we don't have bullish divergences here,
we have that same kind of pattern. We
have pretty bearish divergence here on
the daily, though. is is looking that
that this is not looking good on the
daily. The fact that we're rounding down
as we're struggling to make higher
highs, it really does show signs of
exhaustion.
If I had to if I if there's something
that I would like to see on ETH, I would
actually like to come down here [music]
and do something like this. Um,
that would be nice. If Bitcoin has
bullish divergences at 60K and ETH is
down here, that could be a knife ETH a
ninth ETH trade. A nice ETH trade right
there, you know. Nice ETH trade right
there. If you guys You guys know what
I'm saying. Yeah, ETH has no rules. She
doesn't respect anything. ETH.
ETH is the true pancakes. Dusty
E chart looks the same as Bitcoin chart.
It looks a little bit different. Eat
your weight in grams of protein every
day.
Yeah. I mean, protein high, that's the
way to go. High protein. I mean, I just
like to eat a lot of food in general.
All
right, you got to know how your body
works. You have to know how your body
works. And the only way to do that is
trial and error on yourself. All right,
so for me, the way my body works, the
way my body stays strong and lean and
energetic and feeling good and healthy
and all that is I have to I have to be
in the high energy, high in high out,
high energy flux. High input and high
output. All right? I don't do good on
low output, low input. All right? I
don't do well on that. I don't do well
on low output, high input. I get fat.
All right. For me, I have to eat a lot
of calories and I [music] have to be
very active, right? I got to get my
steps in. 20,000 30,000 steps a day. You
know, I have to lift heavy weights,
intense, heavy workouts. And when you
keep the energy high and the energy
output is high, that's how my body kind
of thrives, right? You got to find out
what works for you. The best diet is the
one that you like and the one that makes
you feel good and perform good.
And if you can find a diet that you like
that makes you feel good and have lots
of energy and lots of strength and just
be in a good mood, the byproduct of that
is that you're going to look good,
right? Like you're going to look strong
and healthy if you're strong and
healthy. Like people try and look strong
and healthy by being like sick and
weakly, right? People are like, "Man, if
I just cut my carbs down,
drop my fats and carbs down, eat only
protein
to try and look strong and healthy, when
in reality, they feel like garbage.
Can't get a dang boner cuz they have no
energy. Their body's like, "The last
thing I want to do is make babies. I,
you know, it's impossible to be a baby
machine like Jason Casper if if you
don't have the energy." You know what
I'm saying? So, you got to figure out
what diet works for you. Some people,
they thrive on a vegan diet, like my man
my man uh my man uh Memory Man, he's a
vegan. He's thriving on it. People,
other people, they're thriving on a
carnivore diet. People thrive on low
carb diets, high carb diets, highfat,
lowfat. You got to figure out what works
for you, man. You know, you got to
figure out what works for you.
We should We should check out Space X.
Um,
let's check out SpaceX. Have I started
reloading on spot? Guys, my plan for
spot is the same as it's been since
[music] November, which is yes, I have
started to reaccumulate on spot, you
know. Uh, I'm one/ird in. All right. I'm
hoping for more drops. I'm hoping for
more drops. I'm one/ird in my spot
bitcoin allocation.
Let's take a look at SpaceX. And
remember, we are doing a $500 giveaway
today for Bitbase.
All right. Wow. Look at Look at SpaceX,
guys. Breaking out of the wedge.
Wow. Look at this. Who would have
thought,
you know?
I We could see a squeeze here, you know.
You know, we could see a squeeze here.
Um,
am I still doing a homestead?
Absolutely, man. I mean, I I was just
talking about we have new baby chicks on
the homestead today. Little peepers.
Sweet little baby chicks. They're so
cute. I love baby chicks so much. They
are so dang cute. Whenever we have baby
chicks Oh, and there's there's another
egg hatching there. This morning I was
out there. There's another egg. The
little the little peepers pecking out.
The little peepers pecking out. It's a
blue egg. I wish I could show you, but I
can't. I can't show you guys. Uh maybe I
can.
Maybe I can. Let me see if I can show
you guys. Let's Let's see something
here. All right. Give me one second
here. All right.
All right. All right. This is the baby
chick. One of them popping out from from
the mom. What a cute little baby chick
that is, guys. And then this is another
egg. The eggs are starting to hatch.
Look at that. You could tell what's
about to happen here. And these are all
under the hen, right? These are just
natural natural chickens out there in
the wild, you know? Look at that little
baby chick. Oh, and another cool thing
that happened today is when I was
opening up the chicken coop to check on
the baby chicks.
Another chicken
who it was one like a few years ago.
I've only had one baby chick survive
in the last 3 years. I've only had one
natural born like under the hen baby
chick survive.
>> [music]
>> And when I opened up the coupe to check
on the baby chicks, the chicken who has
survived from being hatched naturally
under the mother, the only one in the
last 3 years, I saw her lay an egg. It
came right out of the hole. My son saw
it, too. I'm like, "Oh, look. It's about
to lay an egg." Kapoom, egg pops out,
grab the dang egg, bring it inside,
crack it open, make an omelette. It
feels good to make an omelette fresh
from your baby chick's butt. There's
nothing like eating an omelette fresh
from your adult baby chick's bottom.
to really fuel. If you if you're talking
about good diet, you got to eat eggs.
You want to get jacked and stacked and
you got to eat the eggs fresh from your
full grown baby chick's bottom,
you know.
But, uh, SpaceX, wow, would you take a
look at this thing? It is breaking out.
Let's check the daily candle.
Like, this could turn into something
big. Like I said, whoever was in the
chat yesterday saying SpaceX is never
going to pump.
I I do feel like a pump is coming on.
Let's put this thing. Let's take it off
log scale. I mean, look at that. You
know, I I say it's a pretty clear break
of a trend line here. Let's see how the
daily candle closes today. Let's see how
the daily candle closes. This would be
an easy squeeze back up to 170. We don't
have much data here, right? The one
thing I would say is there is some
bullish divergence here on the 1 hour as
we're getting higher. [music] We haven't
seen bullish divergence this whole way
down. This is the first time we've seen
bullish divergence here after this whole
way down. And we do have a a a clean
break, a a a clean break. You know what
I'm saying? Um
but big shout out to our our super chat.
Gold is low. What do you think? Yeah,
gold is low. Thank you so much for the
super chat. Um,
but yeah, I hope these baby chicks grow
grow big and strong. You know, [music] I
had a beautiful golden colored baby
chick last year, the only surviving one.
It it it's hard to get them to survive
naturally. I understand why people do
the whole incubator thing and that's
what we usually do. But it's fun to let
the mom do her thing, right, when we
have a broody hen. So anyway,
this chick lived for months. It got big.
It got full feathered. It was a
beautiful golden chicken, full feathers,
golden chicken, full feathered. And then
one day I go out there and it's gone.
It's gone. And I can't find it anywhere.
I'm looking for, you know, a a dead
chicken somewhere. Can't find it
anywhere. And of course, you know, our
chickens free range in like endless
woods. But I think it got picked off by
a bird. I was really sad about that
chick, man. I was I was actually I was
holding back tears. I really loved that
baby chick. I didn't even know if it was
a boy or a girl yet. I was hoping it was
a girl so that it could lay the golden
eggs. You know what I'm saying? So it
could lay those golden eggs.
Only 500 viewers is low. Yeah, it's low,
man. It's low. You know what's so crazy?
In 2024
around like September, October, I was I
was pulling like 2500 3,000 viewers a
stream. It was crazy. All that fame was
getting to my head, you know. I went
out. I bought a gold chain. Pure gold.
24 karat gold chain. Uh a blow fin
chain.
You know, it looks like that green stuff
is actually just I know it [laughter]
looks it's not fake gold. They're just
emeralds, right? But yeah, now now that
crypto's not hot anymore, you know. You
know what? My fan base is just as fickle
as the Bitcoin price herself.
Let's check out gold.
Let's check out gold. So, the way I'm
looking at gold right now, guys, is
this. [music] All right. On the weekly
time frame, there's a very good chance
that we have a nice we do have a nice
low here on gold. All right. We actually
have a nice low because, well,
we're back down toward the bottom of
this sideways range, right? We're pretty
[clears throat] much toward the bottom
here. When it comes to the weekly
levels, I'm not talking about the wicks,
but the candle body closes. we have come
down to
the bottom and [music] we have a bullish
divergence on the weekly here. All
right, if we're going by candle bodies,
not by the wicks, we have the price on
the weekly is getting lower and the
momentum on the weekly is getting
higher, right? And if we go down to the
daily, what do we see? The same thing,
right? We see in general bullish
divergences here as the price is getting
lower. We're seeing the momentum
starting to get higher. Even right here
locally, we have a bullish div. [music]
And this is a higher low that we've made
right here. Okay, so we have made our
first higher low internally. This is
locally. I mean, this this whole thing
could be like just one leg down, right?
There is a case to be made for a long
from around this area here. All right.
Now, the a better long trade on gold and
a beautiful opportunity would be if we
actually did come down and take out this
low from $3,878.40
and we do so with even more bullish
divergence on our daily time frame. Like
the money flow, the momentum continues
to get higher. We get a big wick down.
We get the reclaim. Maybe that wick's a
little too low than what I would like,
but something like this, right? That
would be a much nicer trade opportunity
for me if we're trying to like catch a
knife. That would be really nice because
that looks like a nice low, a nice fake
out. And really, the reason why this is
such an important level is because if we
get a fake out of this low and a
reclaim, it's a very easy invalidation.
Right now, it's a difficult invalidation
because where would we put that
stop-loss, right? Technically, the idea
is not invalid unless we lose this low,
right? But we don't really know [music]
if we're not just going to get a fake
out and then a reclaim. So, it's very
difficult to get long. Now, if we do
something like this, this is telling us,
all right, the market tried to dump, the
market tried to take all this liquidity,
which could very, very easily long
squeeze us back down to 3500 very
easily. But if the market fails to do
that and just takes this liquidity here
and then gets the reclaim, now we have a
very easy invalidation. Right? The the
trade idea is we're getting a fake out
of this low. And where would that fake
out become invalid? Well, if we try to
get a fake out and then make a lower
low, right? This would make a nice
entry. Good risk-to-reward. [music] Um
because yeah, look at this. Like
we have this kind of deal here,
you know, this kind of falling wedge
pattern, however you want to draw it.
You know, you could even pull it back to
here. You could even pull it up to here.
Like this is a pretty bullish looking
pattern, like a like a pretty standard
like retail pattern here. And I mean,
I'm not a big I'm not a big fan of like
trading retail patterns because they're
retail patterns, but I am a big fan of
looking for what's going to wreck a ton
of people. This would wreck a ton of
people. They get ultra like bearish.
We would have hit a really nice support.
We'd have a really clear invalidation.
And this is the kind of knife catch that
I would be interested in, right?
Actually would be interested in this.
Um, [music] pull a fib from high to low.
And I'd say we could shoot for a nice
TP1 right around here. It's a 5 to1
riskreward give or take. Let's pull the
volume.
Okay. So, the PC
that's still a 4:1 risk-reward ratio at
that PC. Let's take it from the high.
Yeah, I'd say about about this would be
our our TP1 on the idea. But here's the
thing. Once we're reclaiming this,
right, then we could TP1. But we would
look to we would look to compound it if
we come back down, right? We would look
for that kind of accumulation pattern,
that rounded bottom. So, we would go for
the nice catch on the fake out, hit TP1
at the first resistance,
and then look to add to the trade as we
come back down to test 4,000, and then
we could see that thing continue to play
out, right? That that would be a nice
setup on gold. All right. Yeah, I
remember I used to get 1,000 likes in
half an hour. Now we have 180 likes.
It's been an hour.
You know, feeling the leg down on gold.
Yeah. would be nice.
Fingerless gloves look cooler. Dave
Digital doesn't look mittens. He wears
fingerless gloves. They do look pretty
cool. [music] Fingerless gloves. Um I
remember I used to try and wear them at
one point in my life to try and look
cool. And Jason Casper, he doesn't I
don't I don't do I just can't look cool,
guys. All right. I've come to terms with
the fact that I'm not cool. stopped
raining just enough time for me to go go
pee in the bushes.
Man, look at how gray it is outside.
It's so gray out.
The garbage can blew over in the wind.
Let's see here.
Uh
I got to feel an Alex O will never ever
lose another trading wars. Shout out to
Alex O.
Yeah, we can take a look at Micro
Strategy. Remember, we got to uh we are
going to be giving away $500 today. All
right,
man. It feels good to take a pee.
There's nothing like taking a pee after
after holding it. You know, it was
raining so hard. I thought I'd never get
to pee,
you know. Sheesh, man.
Uh
yeah, I had to account for like
inflation. What about a collab with MM
Crypto? Man, I would love to collab with
MM Crypto, but you know what? I don't
think MM Crypto would ever collab with
me. You know what I'm saying? He's too
rich and famous. He's too rich and
famous for to collab with a a guy like
Jason Casper.
You know, he's too rich and famous.
All right, let's get back up on the on
the treadmill, baby.
All right, we're going to take a look at
at Master Strategy Micro Micro Strategy.
All right, shout out to Zach 61ita.
Um, big shouts out to Zach 61ita.
All right, let's see here.
>> MSTR
Micro Strategy.
What's it going to be for Micro
Strategy?
Let's go to the weekly on Micro
Strategy.
Right. So, honestly, we have the bottom
of the bare market mapped out. That's
our green vertical line. We do have a
bullish div on the weekly just like
Bitcoin. All right. But this green box
is our resistance here. Okay. So, as
long as we're not able to reclaim $100.
I'd say lower is still more probable.
We front ran value area low
by like a couple bucks. Did we?
>> Did we front run that? Hang on. No, we
didn't front it. But we al we front ran
the weekly fair value gap by by
literally a couple bucks.
Um, I would like to see this thing dump
down to $58 value area high back test.
If we could do that, if we could do
something like this,
you know, get a big old capitulation by
October and then come back in here, then
maybe we could see this thing go up. If
there if there is a micro strategy in
the future, this might be the end of
Micro Strategy.
This might be the end, right? This might
be the end of it, but it might not be.
But, uh, it could be the end of it. It
could be the end of it honestly. You
know
what do you think about that?
What do you think about it's the end of
micro strategy? What are your thoughts
on that? You know
you were peeing in the bushes too. Pink.
Yeah. Peeing in the bushes. That's the
way to go. You know
that is the way to go.
Helping the tree grow. Yeah, [music]
I love to pee in the tree. In fact, my
wife, she got me a sticker that I put on
my door. It says, "I love to pee
outside." I do love to pee outside.
It's moon from here, Jason. I spoke to
Trump. Shout out to Error Epic 007.
Micro Strategy is doomed. Yeah, could be
the end. I know a lot of people, you
know, feel like it it could never fail.
I mean, what could go wrong? was just a
guy who's had every other business go
bankrupt in the history of all his
businesses. Who all of a sudden used AI
apparently to come up with this business
model that just can't fail.
Just can't fail. It's impossible.
Hector Rodriguez says we don't have
bushes here. Um
you don't have bushes.
You then you got to get out of the city,
man. Honestly, you got to get out of you
got to get into the country, guys. If
you're not in the country, I don't know.
I don't know what you're doing. You're
still in the city. I don't know what
you're doing. City is where everything
bad happens.
The city is literally where everything
bad happens. All right. The country,
that's the place where just you chill.
You live a nice, quiet, chill life. You
know, country is where it's at.
It's just a matter of time.
Shout out to Joanie HSV from Germany.
Do I remember you? I don't really
remember you. I'll be honest, Joanie
HSV. I mean, I remember you from
yesterday, but I don't remember you from
like times past, you know. No offense or
anything, but look, you know, I've had
so many there's been so many chapters of
Jason Casper live chat people and people
in the Discord,
you know, that it's it's hard to
remember people. You know, you have
people in here and you think they're
they're they're like regulars and then
all of a sudden they disappear. You
know, they disappear.
You live in your country and in your
city. Nah, you got to get out of the
city into the countryside, my friend.
You know,
the countryside. Exactly. Micro Strategy
could very well be the next FTX. Maybe
even worse. We'll see in a few months.
Exactly. That's what I'm thinking
myself. You know,
Dave Digital from India. Yeah, man. I
remember you. I remember you, bro. I
remember you, man.
Man.
Man. Man.
Man, let's check it out here. Who the
heck?
[music]
Did I notice your Bitcoin key resistance
level pretty much matches with the 4hour
local PC? Yeah. Yep. It's a support
resistance flip and a PC, you know.
Whoa. Can't show that on here. Hang on
one second. That was a close one.
When I wear my hat like this, does it
make me feel empowered?
Oh yeah, man. There's nothing like
wearing your hat like this. Especially
out in public. You feel super empowered.
You feel brave. You feel like a hero.
You feel like a brave hero. Honestly,
when I wear my hat like this, I feel
just as brave as Bruce Jenner when he
chopped off his ding-dong.
Shout out to Sergio Jay. I was at a
concert with four chicks back in my 20s.
Do I remember me? Of course, man. You're
that guy with those four girls. Yeah, of
course I remember you, man. Of course I
remember you.
Crap. Did I show my seed phrase on
stream? Did you guys actually see that?
You didn't see that. Look, if it happens
quick, it doesn't count. Doesn't count.
You saw it. Crap.
Dang.
Am I live 24/7? By the grace of God, for
the past 35 almost 36 years, I have been
alive 24/7.
And by the grace of God and by his
mercy, I'll make it until I'm 120.
120.
You know,
Sea Train disappeared. He'll be back.
Things get a little weird after 40.
Nothing horrible, [music] but it wakes
you up a lot. Regroup, reset, come back
and chill with some good people. Shout
out to Sea Train, man. I'm heading I'm
heading toward 40 myself, you know. I I
I consider myself 50 already cuz I'm
basically 40. I'm about to be 36 in a
week. I'll be 36 in a week and then you
might as well be 40. And if you're 40,
you honestly might as well be 50.
You might as well be 50 cuz cuz to be
honest with you guys, 26 feels like
that, right? 26 feels like boom, [music]
right? So
26 goes by like that. That means I'm
going to be 50 like that. And once
you're 50, you might as well be 70.
Honestly, once you're 70, you might as
well be 80. And then once you're 80, you
might as well be 100. And then boom,
baby, we're 120. You know what I'm
saying?
You know, you're not supposed to label
the seed phrase seed phrase. Crap. Dang
it.
Senor says he's 41 this year. Best times
of his life. Praise the Lord, Senor.
Praise the Lord. You know,
wasn't Noah 900.
I don't think Noah was 900.
I'll have to check. You know, I used to
have Genesis 5 memorized in Hebrew,
man. I used to have the first nine
chapters of Genesis memorized in Hebrew,
guys.
And I forgot it. I still probably could
I could probably recite verses here and
there if someone started, but man, I
forget the ages. I know [music]
Adam was 930. I think Seth Seth was 95.
I forget how old Enosh was now.
Man,
I know Methuselo was 969.
Lamach lived to be 777, I think. Right.
I You know what? I don't remember. How
old was Noah when he died?
I know he was 600 years old when the
when the flood came,
you know.
Uh let's see.
Uh big shout out to real Noranon who
says add Maya Vasim as we say. Well,
that's cool. Uh,
shout out to Felix H who says, "Praise
Jesus." Amen, bro. Praise the Lord. Once
you're 120, you might as well live
forever. Yeah. Well, I believe I will
live forever.
Did I really have it memorized if I
forgot? That's a good question, Dave
Digital. That's a great question. I
guess not. I guess not, you [music]
know. I guess not, man.
I suppose not, you know.
But um yeah, I you know my my goal was
to memorize the entire Torah in Hebrew
to memorize the the Pentatuk in Hebrew,
the five books, the first five books of
the Bible. My goal was to memorize that
in Hebrew. And at the rate I was
memorizing, I would have had the whole
thing memorized by the time I was 65.
All right.
Sadly
sadly, I don't think that'll happen now,
guys. It's never too late, but uh
I don't think it'll happen now. All
right.
Don't think it'll happen.
Yeah, I don't understand the super chat,
uh, real Norman, but you know, I I I
appreciate it, man. You know, thank
[music] you. Thank you. Thank you for
the super chat.
Shout out to Remy, who says, "Jesus
healed me from anxiety."
Do I know Brian Johnson?
Is that the uh the liver king?
No, it was 950. Okay,
you know,
shout out to Dave Digital. He I saw a
guy on the internet. His I think his
name was Jason Gasper. He told me, "If
you don't think it will happen, then it
won't happen." Yeah, that's true. You
know,
boom. Yeah, you, Alex, and the lifer
helped me a lot through life.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Shout out to Crypto Lifer.
Shout out to Alex O. Two of the best in
the world. And we got to give a big
shout out to Crypto Lifer Sam Price for
being the best.
>> Uh it's between him and Gio who covered
the pump song the best. But here's uh
Sam Price singing the pump song.
We're going to bump. No, we're going to
dump. We're going to bump. No, we're
going to dump. We're going to bump. No,
we're going to dump. We're going to
bump. [groaning]
We're going to bump. No, we're going to
dump. We're going to bomb. No, we're
going to dump. We're going to bump. No,
we're going to dump. We're going to
bump. [groaning]
We're going to bump. No, we're going to
dump. Sorry, I got stuck on it. I got
stuck on it.
Big shouts to our super chat, the real
Norman. He says,
he says, "Up until
120," as we say in Hebrew.
Yeah, I'm trying to live up until 120,
man. For sure.
Have I read the Quran? Of course. Of
course I've read the Quran. Who hasn't
read the If you've never read the Quran,
put a one in the chat.
Oh,
shout out to memory man. Sorry guys, I
got stuck. I got stuck. Couldn't change
the screen back. Oh my goodness.
But no, big shout out to Sam Price
because honestly Sam Price is a good
guy. [music] I've I've chilled with him
a few times. All right, and he he's a
great guy. What can I say? He's a good
guy, you know? I really like him a lot.
I like him. I like his wife. I like his
family. My kids like his kids. I don't
know if his kids like my kids. I never
asked them, but my kids like their kids.
They think they're cool. So, big shout
out to Sam Price, man. dude's put puts
in the work. All right. [music]
Seriously, he's in he's in here every
single day doing the analysis. One of
the few [music] crypto channels that I
actually
watch or listen to, should I say. I
usually listen to Sam Price when I'm
doing my morning farm chores. You know,
uh,
you know, doing my morning farm chores
out there looking at checking on the
baby chicks. See how the baby chicks are
doing,
you know. Let's see. Where's the baby?
Ay, see how the baby chicks are doing?
Checking on the eggs, listening to Sam
Price talk about the Bitcoin price and
all the other assets. You know what I'm
saying?
Wow. A lot of people never read the
Quran.
my view of on the Talmud.
Uh, well, here's here's my here's my
view. All right, the Tal a lot of people
misunderstand the Talmud. All right,
it's just commentary. It's just a whole
bunch of rabbis throughout history
[music] commentating on
the Mishna
pretty much. And
there's a lot of different views in the
Talmud on a lot of different things. You
can't just read the Talab and say the
Talmud says the Talmud as a book has
this teaching on this subject. You can't
just say that. It's a whole bunch of
different rabbis arguing about a whole
bunch of different things
throughout history. All right. So
[music]
that it's it's not it's kind of like an
online forum in a way of everyone just
kind of giving their commentary, right?
It's not a distinct book. It's a whole
bunch of different
people and they're giving their views
and their comment. They're they're
they're making comments on other
comments that people have made, right?
It's commentary on commentary basically.
Um, what do I think about rabbitic
Judaism? Like modern rabbitic Judaism. I
think it's a false religion. I think
modern rabbitic Judaism,
you know, after
after the temple was destroyed in 70 AD,
Judaism as a religion had to be
completely reinvented. Had to be
completely reinvented. And it's 100%
man-made. And in my opinion, you know,
well, never mind. I don't want to go too
deep into what my opinion is, but I
think I think it's a whole bunch of
nonsense. I think it's a whole bunch of
nonsense. All right. I know that it
would offend a lot of people, but I
think it's a whole bunch of nonsense.
Exactly. Rabbitic Judaism is not Yeah.
It's a modern invention. It's a modern
invention of man. That's really what it
is. All right. It is what it is. It is
what it is.
Are we going to 60K?
Yeah. And a lot of it is mixed with the
ancient mystery religion. That's another
thing, too. A a lot of rabbitic Judaism
is mixed with the same ancient pagan
religion that got them that got the
ancient Israelites in trouble in the
first place.
So that's that's that's kind of my
opinion on it. Now
I'm not
>> not everything in the Talmud is bad. Not
everything in rabbitic Judaism is bad
either. Just like not
there's one way to judge anything and
it's does it line up with what God said?
Right? If it lines up with what God said
then it's fine. If it doesn't line up or
contradicts what God said then it's not
fine. It's that simple. It's that
simple.
>> Do I think it's funny when that one guy
calls people potato? Actually don't know
what you're talking about, Dave Digital.
I'll be honest with you. I don't know.
I've never seen that.
Um,
yeah, rebbitic Judaism is anti-
Jesus pymics. A lot of it is. A lot of
it is. I mean, I'm reading a very
interesting book right now.
I'm reading a very interesting book
right now that uh
>> I would uh I would recommend it if
anyone's into
the uh
the history of
you know
it's Yeah. Let me let me send this book
to you guys right now.
See here.
Check out this book.
It's a good book.
It's called The Ways That Never Parted.
Jews and Christians in the late
antiquity and early middle ages. And it
really goes into all that stuff, you
know, the reaction that the synagogue
reacts to the church, the church reacts
to the synagogue.
They influence each other. It's very
interesting. It's very interesting
if you're into that kind of stuff,
you know.
What?
We got a lot of lot a lot of interesting
things in the chat.
A lot of interesting lot of interesting
The Pentecost video.
Yeah, if you guys I have a Bible
channel.
Let's see here.
I have a Bible channel. If you're
interested in biblical topics and you
want to hear a purple hat treadmill guy
talk to you about them,
you can go to the Billy Casper
Bible channel,
the Billy Casper Bible Channel. And you
can check out all these videos.
All right, all these videos,
deep teachings. I'm currently teaching
through the Gospel of John verse by
verse. All right? Verse by verse. And if
anyone wants to know why I'm dressed
like this, it's because we are a
congregation of Messianic Jews. All
right? We are Jewish people and
non-Jewish people who know that Jesus
Yeshua is the Messiah. All right? I
always get questions when people see me
in a synagogue with a keepa and a talit.
All right? They're like, "Jason, what's
the deal, bro?" That's the deal. All
right?
That's the deal. All right. So, if
you're if you want more, check it out.
[music] The commercials are nuts today.
Golden Child says, "If religion is
claiming people live to 900 years, it's
probably BS. I'm honestly blown away
that intelligent people can read that
stuff and not question the rest of the
stories."
Okay. Well, I mean, there's there's a
lot of different views on that.
Um, actually, you know what? If you want
a
a real scholar, an actual Bible scholar,
if if let's say, for example, you're the
kind of person that says, you know what,
I just can't believe somebody could live
for 900 years. Personally, I don't have
a problem with it. But let's say you're
the kind of person that thinks, you know
what, I just can't I can't believe that
somebody could live to 900 years. You
know what? Check this guy out. All
right. This guy is an actual biblical
scholar. He makes some really cool
content.
Um,
and his view on that is that it's it's
not actually uh literal. It's not
literal. Uh, yeah. Let's see. Let's see
if I could find that video. It's
interesting. His view is interesting.
[music] And the reason why he has that
view is because he studies the ancient
near east cultures and the way they use
genealogies. All right. So, see if I
could find that.
I don't know
if I could find that video right now cuz
I'm looking for it. Cuz I'm looking for
it. You know, when you're looking for
something live, you'll never find it.
You'll never [music] find it. But
anyway, if that's the only thing keeping
you from believing in the Bible,
there are there are other explanations
besides the fact that people live that
long.
I wish I could find it, man. It was a
very interesting video. This guy's like
a he's like a Michael Heiser type. All
right. He's like a Michael Heiser type
but more uh less scholarly, but he
actually is a real Bible scholar.
Um but yeah, if you're into like the
ancient like the especially like the
Torah and like the the beginning of
Genesis and all that stuff, this guy is
the guy. All right. This guy is the guy.
Maybe something this the 6,000-year
timeline. Man, let me see if I could
find it.
This is a good channel, man. I'm telling
you.
Aha, here we go. Yeah, check this one
out here. Check this one out here.
>> Along the way, I'll even ask,
>> I think,
uh, yeah, check out this video. I'll
post in the chat. All right,
post in the chat.
Yeah, and this is true. Memory Man says,
"You can always find evidence of what
you always believe." It's called
confirmation bias. Confirmation bias,
right? You you already believe the
Bible's true, so you're going to you're
going to look for any kind of evidence
you can just to grasp onto. It's called
confirmation bias. Everyone has it.
Yeah, it's true. It's true. Everyone has
it. I have it. I mean, I already I
already believe that Jesus saved me. I
already believe Yeshua is the Messiah.
that was that was foretold by Moses and
the prophets.
I already believe that no matter what
cuz I've experienced him. So yeah, I've
got mad confirmation bias. It's totally
true, [music]
you know. It's totally true.
I need to stop the Once Upon a Time
stuff and get back to Bitcoin. Well, I
don't know. We've been live for an hour
and a half. We kind of talked about it.
Oh, shout out to LA. He He watches that
guy, too. Yeah, that's what's up.
You know, that's what's up.
Yeah, they ate Whole Foods back then.
That's why they live so long.
But, you know, I
I just feel like things were different
back then. You know,
about the Nikoni Codeex. Yeah. You know
what? Uh, Memory Man, that same YouTube
channel has a lot of content about that,
too. I think you might be interested in
his what he has to say about it.
Oh, yeah. We have to do a giveaway.
Let's do a giveaway, guys. All right, so
here's the deal. We're going to give
away $500.
All right, we're going to give away $500
courtesy of Bitbase. All right, now
[music] remember, we do this every week
here. Every single week. We do it every
single week. [music] So, let me just
double check something real quick here.
Yeah, every single week. So, here's what
we're going to do, guys. We are going to
give away $500 based on Bitbase.
All right. So, you need to have a
Bitbase account using my link. All
right. You need to have a Bitbase
account using my link.
Uh, and the way we're going to do it is
I want you to spam the chat
with your
Let's see. I have to get back to the
live stream. Spam the chat with your
user ID for Bitbase.
and we will select a user ID [music] and
give that person $500. All right. If you
don't have a user ID for Bitbase, guess
what? It's not too late because every
single week we're going to do it. Also,
remember, Blofin is giving away $2,000
a week. All right? So, if you want more
chances to win, sign up for Blowin and
join my free Discord.
All right. All right. So, let's see
here. Let's go, baby. Let's count down
from 10 and see who the winner is. 10 9
7 6 5 4 3 2 1 boom. All right. And the
winner is
shout out to Jackal
7676.
Jackal 7676. I'm going to send you to
Bitbase right now, man.
Shout out to our winner. Big shouts.
Congratulations.
I've got patience to say
congratulations.
You know,
shout out to our winner, Jackal.
Some grass man.
Yeah, I I I do want to come down to 60K
for BTC, man. Shout out to Jackal.
Congrats, bro. Yeah, they'll send that
over to you. All right. They'll send
that over to you, man.
Shout out to Jack Jackal 7676.
Yeah. 7676. Guys, tomorrow is FOMC.
We're going to be live for FOMC. It's
going to be a It's going to be a banger
of a show or it's going to be a banger
of a show.
It's going to be a banger. So, make sure
not to miss it. Make sure not to miss
it. [music] All right, with that being
said, guys, I think I'm going to head
out. God bless you all in Jesus name. I
do pray y'all and your families are
super blessed. And I'll see you guys,
Lord willing, tomorrow for FOMC. Peace.